A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Counsel's Office, Series 10 FA358
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Michael Whiteman, 1963-1974; 4; 80 Document Box(es)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Children, 1972-1974 (Box 41, Folder 439)
    Proposal to create Commission on Services to Children and Youth, memos, notes, proposed bill, report of Board of Social Welfare on project placement.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Children's Recreation Foundation - Senator Robert Kennedy, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 440)
    Funds from a Professional Golfers Association (PGA) Tournament at Deepdale Country Club correspondence.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Cigarette Tax Enforcement, January-April 1972 (Box 41, Folder 441)
    Bootlegging: memo, studies, analysis, correspondence, history.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Cigarette Tax Enforcement, May-December 1972 (Box 41, Folder 442)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Cigarette Tax Enforcement (Box 42, Folder 443)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Civil Rights - Shield Law (Box 42, Folder 444)
    Memo, excerpt from "Congressional Record," United States Senate bills.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Civil Service, 1973, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 445)
    1. Memos re: reclassification of position of Director of Syracuse Psychiatric Hospital, 1973 2. memos re: reclassification of criminal investigator in Westchester District Attorney's office, 1970
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Clemency, 1967-1968 (Box 42, Folder 446)
    1. 1967 applications 2. 1968 "Christmas package" 3. 1968 applications
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Clemency, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 447)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Clemency, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 448)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Clemency, 1970-1974 (Box 42, Folder 449)
    L. Judson Morhous -- memos, press release, medical affidavits, file sent to Counsel, House Judiciary Committee for use in Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential proceedings, 1974.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Clemency, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 450)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Clemency (Box 43, Folder 451)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Clemency, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 452)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - City University, 1970-1972 (Box 43, Folder 453)
    Reports of Citizens' Commission on the Future, memos.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - College Campus Disorders, 1969-1972 (Box 43, Folder 454)
    Letters to students at Notre Dame University from President Reverend Hesburgh, drafts of letter by Nelson A. Rockefeller, Nelson A. Rockefeller press release re: Cornell disturbance in April 1969, copy of "Temporary Commission to Study Cause of Campus Unrest (Preliminary Third Report), 1972".
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Commercial Rent Control, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 455)
    Memos and correspondence.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Community Development Constitutional Amendment (Box 43, Folder 456)
    Objections by Commerce and Industry Association, memos by Hugh Morrow and Stephen Lefkowitz of Urban Development Association.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Commutations, 1969-1973 (Box 43, Folder 457)
    Violation of Governor's commutation; memos -- new rules 1973.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Compensation - Auto Victims, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 458)
    No-fault correspondence, editorials.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Conference of Mayors (Box 43, Folder 459)
    Lobbying issues.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Constitutional Amendments, 1969-1973 (Box 43, Folder 460)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Consumer Protection Board, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 461)
    Memos, question of continuance.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Copyright Policy, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 462)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory, 1969-1972 (Box 44, Folder 463)
    Correspondence re: sale of lab to an independent, for-profit entity.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Correctional Services, 1971-1972 (Box 44, Folder 464)
    Report on Auburn Prison disturbance of November 1970; Russell Oswald address before House Select Committee on Crime, November 30, 1971; memos on prison reform, memos on prison labor, memos and clippings on Attica Prison riot.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Corrections Ombudsman Program, 1972-1973 (Box 44, Folder 465)
    Correspondence and memos from Correctional Association.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Correctional Services - New York City Contract, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 466)
    Memos re: housing of New York City inmates in state prisons.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Counsel's Office Issues, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 467)
    1. Counsel's office -- miscellaneous policy memos 2. Assistant Counsel -- staffing memos
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Court Congestion, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 468)
    Letter from Legal Aid Society and copy of 2nd Circuit Court of Appeals brief.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Court of Claims, 1969-1973 (Box 44, Folder 469)
    1. Clerk vacancy -- application of John R. Stuart, 1973 2. court report -- Judge Young, 1970 3. Court of Claims -- vacancy applications, 1969
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Court of Claims - Resumes (Box 44, Folder 470)
    Submitted for appointment to court.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Court of Claims - Candidates (Box 44, Folder 471)
    First round.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Court of Appeals, 1968-1973 (Box 44, Folder 472)
    Vacancies and appointments.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Drug Program (Box 44, Folder 473)
    Judicial screening and panel -- appointment and recommendation.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Drug Program (Box 45, Folder 474)
    Lists of judges, resumes.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Courts - Emergency Felony Cases (Box 45, Folder 475)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Courts - Special Narcotics Parts, 1970-1974 (Box 45, Folder 476)
    Reports, proposals, correspondence.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Courts - New York City Housing Court (Box 45, Folder 477)
    Correspondence on finding of court -- is city or state responsible.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Issues, 1968-1971 (Box 45, Folder 478)
    Court reform -- background.
    See also Folders 479-482.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Court Reform, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 479)
    Reports, studies, memos.
    See also Folders 478.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Court Reform, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 480)
    Reports and memos.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Court Reform, 1969-1972 (Box 45, Folder 481)
    Judicial selection.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Court Reform, 1971-1974 (Box 46, Folder 482)
    "Fordham Law Review" article on judicial removal (1971); report -- Administration of Criminal Courts (1972); Report to Administrative Board of the Judicial Conference (1972); Whiteman memo to Nelson A. Rockefeller re: report of Temporary State Commission on the Courts (1972) with proposed legislation; revised preliminary report of Joint Committee on Court Reorganization (1974); constitutional amendment proposal by Federal Judge Jack B. Weinstein (1973); Chief Judge Brietel press release on complaints against Judges (1974); Chief Judge Brietel speech to legislature on court reorganization (1974); New York County lawyers report on court reform (1974); New York State Commission of Investigation report on discipline of judiciary (1974).
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Victims of Violent Crime, 1965-1968 (Box 46, Folder 483)
    Memos, articles, reports, proposed legislation.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Joint Legislative Committee on Crime, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 484)
    Correspondence, memos, proposed legislation.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Crime Control Planning Board, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 485)
    Memos re: board membership (Richard Bartlett).
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Criminal Procedures (Box 46, Folder 486)
    Speedy trial rules, memos.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - DeVeaux School Finances, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 487)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Direct Primary, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 488)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Drug Issues, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 489)
    1. Drug program administration meeting, November 12, 1973 (meeting cancelled) 2. drug law -- memos, brochures 3. drug program -- judge appointments
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Drug Laws - Temporary State Commission, 1970-1972 (Box 47, Folder 490)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Economic Advisers - State Council, 1968-1969 (Box 47, Folder 491)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Ecuadorian "Bombers", 1970 (Box 47, Folder 492)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Education Department, 1969-1974 (Box 47, Folder 493)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Education Aid Formula (Box 47, Folder 494)
    Draft outline for Board of Cooperative Education Services (BOCES) and Council of Economic Advisors (CEA).
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Higher Education Financing, 1972-1974 (Box 47, Folder 495)
    Regents' legislative proposals FY 1973-1974, Lt. Governor's proposal November 14, 1972, Keppel Task Force (1973), Regents' 1974 proposals.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Higher Education Planning, 1971-1974 (Box 47, Folder 496)
    Regents' planning.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Higher Education Task Force (Box 47, Folder 497)
    Memos, Nelson A. Rockefeller press conference (February 15, 1972).
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Higher Education Task Force, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 498)
    Meetings, studies, memos. Governor Wilson press conference (September 29, 1974), reports.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - PAROCHAID - Aid to Parochial Schools, 1969-1973 (Box 47, Folder 499)
    Memos, reports, correspondence, legislative proposals, court cases.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Education - Impounded Federal Funds (Box 48, Folder 500)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Education - Libraries, 1971-1972 (Box 48, Folder 501)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Education - Special School Districts, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 502)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Election Law (Box 48, Folder 503)
    Political calendar.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - 80 Centre Street (New York City), 1972-1973 (Box 48, Folder 504)
    Memos re: use of space by others.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Eminent Domain Commission, 1971-1974 (Box 48, Folder 505)
    Memos re: appointments to Commission, correspondence, reports.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Employee Parking Fees - Public Employment Relations Board (PERB) Decision Ordering Negotiation, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 506)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Employee Relations (Box 48, Folder 507)
    Pleadings in lawsuit brought by 3 employees laid off because of budget cuts.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Employee Relations, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 508)
    Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Easter weekend strike -- memos.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Employee Negotiations, 1972-1973 (Box 48, Folder 509)
    Memos, fact finders, reports on State University of New York (SUNY) professionals and state troopers, legislative bills comparisons, draft legislation, memos on negotiations.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Employee Negotiations, April 23-May 20, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 510)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Employee Negotiations, May 21, 1973-March 1974 (Box 49, Folder 511)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Employer Relations Memoranda (Box 49, Folder 512)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Employee Negotiations, 1967-1968 (Box 49, Folder 513)
    Memos, Public Employment Relations Board (PERB) decision, press release.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Environmental Bond Issue, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 514)
    Memos, publicity planning, television ads, propaganda.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Equalization and Assessment, 1969-1973 (Box 49, Folder 515)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Extradition (Box 49, Folder 516)
    Miscellaneous staff memos on law of extradition.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Federal Judgeships, 1972-1973 (Box 49, Folder 517)
    Recommendations, internal memos and evaluations.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Federal Revenue Sharing - New York City, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 518)
    Memo from M. Whiteman to R. Dunham (budget).
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Flood of 1972 (Box 49, Folder 519)
    Memo re: disaster relief to Corning-Elmira area, question of aid to Catholic schools.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - General Services- Shooter's Island (New York City Harbor) (Box 49, Folder 520)
    Correspondence re: clean-up of debris.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Gift Tax, 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 521)
    Memos re: impact of gift tax on residents moving out of state.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Goodell Appointment to United States Senate (Robert F. Kennedy Vacancy), 1972 (Box 50, Folder 522)
    Research memo, appointment, Nelson A. Rockefeller press release, Goodell press release.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Grave Diggers Strike (Box 50, Folder 523)
    Memos, board of inquiry report, Nelson A. Rockefeller executive order for compulsory arbitration.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Issues, 1967-1969 (Box 50, Folder 524)
    1. Harness tracks -- budget reports and Governor's budget bill 2. Harness Track Improvement Fund -- report on proposed improvements, 1969
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Health Research, Incorporated (Box 50, Folder 525)
    Memo to A. G. Marshall from Richard Dunham re: insolvency of corporation.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Held Committee (Box 50, Folder 526)
    Correspondence re: budgeting layoffs.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - New York State Historical Trust (Box 50, Folder 527)
    Resignation of Chairman Jones.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - New York City Housing Development Corporation, 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 528)
    Lt. Governor's memo of concern re: "moral makeup" and responsive memo.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Housing Finance Agency, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 529)
    Annual report for 1971, memos re: increasing bonding limits.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Insurance Department, 1972-1974 (Box 50, Folder 530)
    Correspondence, undated (c. February 1973) draft report on competitive rating law.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - "Hurd v. Buffalo", 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 531)
    Litigation: Court of Appeals invalidated legislation allowing City of Buffalo to exclude from its constitutional tax limit the amounts raised to cover certain pension and retirement liabilities.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Hudson River Expressway, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 532)
    Litigation: Citizens Committee for the Hudson Valley and the Sierra Club sued state seeking to stop planning for construction of the "Hudson River Expressway," correspondence.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Hudson River Valley Commission, 1966-1968 (Box 50, Folder 533)
    Legislation creating compact with federal government, miscellaneous correspondence.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Human Rights Issues, 1971-1974 (Box 51, Folder 534)
    1. Human Rights Appeals Board miscellaneous correspondence 2. Assemblyman Margiotta's community stabilization plan 3. private universities -- 1971 study of the need for legislation to protect the interest of devout students, Nelson A. Rockefeller veto of legislation, correspondence
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Insurance - "Sacks v. Stewart", 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 535)
    Federal lawsuit brought by former employee of Insurance Department claiming wrongful discharge and seeking damages.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Insurance Tax, 1970-1973 (Box 51, Folder 536)
    1. Insurance tax: memos on effect on insurance companies of increase in taxes on them by 1973 legislation 2. insurance: interest rate on life insurance policy loans
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Interfaith Hospital - Drug Rehabilitation, 1968-1973 (Box 51, Folder 537)
    Memos re: operational problems, news clipping reporting conviction of operator for theft of Medicaid funds.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Interstate Planning Compact (Box 51, Folder 538)
    Between New York, New Jersey, and Connecticut to engage in transportation and land use planning -- memos and legislation.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Iroquois Wampum, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 539)
    Possessed by New York State Museum -- Return sought by Iroquois, correspondence, Education Department, New York State Council on the Arts.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Ithaca Festival and Arts Center, 1967-1969 (Box 51, Folder 540)
    Proposal, fundraising efforts, please to Nelson A. Rockefeller and Rockefeller Brothers Fund to save the project, promotional materials, publicity efforts, audio tape.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Job Discrimination - Gender, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 541)
    News clippings and memos re: conflict between federal and state laws concerning limits on hours and shifts of women.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Judicial Selection (Box 52, Folder 542)
    Appointment of judges to Court of Claims, order dismissing declaratory judgment complaint, correspondence and memos.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Judicial Salaries, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 543)
    Memos re: increasing judges salaries and parity in different courts.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Eugene Gold - Kings County District Attorney's Office, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 544)
    Investigation of District Attorney's office -- Police Officer Stephen Spinelli's testimony before House Select Committee on Crime.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Labor (Box 52, Folder 545)
    1. General 2. agricultural 3. fair labor standards
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Labor - Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), 1971-1974 (Box 52, Folder 546)
    Correspondence, memos, reports on issue of New York State retaining jurisdiction over workers' safety by adopting federal plan.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Law Revision Commission, 1969-1973 (Box 52, Folder 547)
    Memo re: mission of Commission, annual reports.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Legislature (Box 52, Folder 548)
    Michael Whiteman report to Nelson A. Rockefeller on bills, Michael Whiteman memo to Nelson A. Rockefeller re: Senator Anderson's critique of vetoes, miscellaneous memos.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Legislative and Judicial Salaries, 1968-1974 (Box 53, Folder 549)
    State Commission reports 1971 and 1973, memos.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Local Assistance, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 550)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Malverne Schools, 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 551)
    Funding predominantly black schools -- correcting racial imbalance program.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Management Improvement Council, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 552)
    Memo of meeting.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Medicaid, 1966-1972 (Box 53, Folder 553)
    Proposals, cutbacks, litigation; "Report of New York County Grand Jury December 10, 1971."
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Mental Hygiene, 1966, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 554)
    1. Bronx Children's Psychiatric Hospital -- payroll fraud 2. institutional strike at Creedmoor Hospital, 1968: memos, strike notice, injunction, Public Employment Relations Board (PERB)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - State of New York Mortgage Agency (SONYMA - Sonny Mac), 1970-1973 (Box 53, Folder 555)
    Memoranda, bond sale information, Internal Revenue Service (IRS) ruling requests.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Metropolitan Transit Authority, 1969, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 556)
    Financing rapid transit system, correspondence, proposed bill.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Metropolitan Transit Authority - Long Island Railroad Strike (Box 53, Folder 557)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Moratorium, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 0557A)
    Memo re: government spending.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Municipal Ethics, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 0557B)
    Proposed new law, memo, news clipping.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Narcotic Addiction Control Commissions, 1968-1970 (Box 54, Folder 558)
    Correspondence, reports, 1970 strike.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Narcotics Implementation, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 559)
    Correspondence, press releases; more judges, jails, penalties.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - National Governor's Conference, 1969, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 560)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - National Guard, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 561)
    Service obligation of members of Guard activated during March 1970 postal strike.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - National Disaster Relief, 1972-1973 (Box 54, Folder 562)
    Memos re: post-flood relief -- Hurricane Agnes -- June 1972.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Neuberger Art Collection, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 563)
    Gift to State University of New York (SUNY)-Purchase, correspondence, deed of gift.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - National Council on Crime and Delinquency - Organized Crime, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 564)
    Conference materials.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - New York City - Human Resources Administration, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 565)
    News clipping re: theft; letter of explanation from Myles J. Lane.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - New York City - Charter Revision Commission, 1972-1974 (Box 54, Folder 566)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - New York City - Mitchell-Lama Program, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 567)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - New York City - Office of Collective Bargaining, 1970-1972 (Box 54, Folder 568)
    City council laws, Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB) annual reports, possible Taylor Law legislation.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - New York City - Fiscal Affairs, 1968-1969 (Box 55, Folder 569)
    Mayor Lindsay's budget proposal for state aid.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - New York City - Rent Control, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 570)
    WCBS Editorial, Gemma letter.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - New York City - Superceder, Corruption, 1972-1974 (Box 55, Folder 571)
    Appointment of Maurice Nadjari -- Special Prosecutor; memos, executive order, press releases, (bad press 1973).
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - New York City - School Decentralization, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 572)
    Memos, position papers, correspondence, bill comparisons.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - New York City - School Strike, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 573)
    Memos, correspondence, telegrams, "New York Times" article.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - New York City - Teachers' Strike, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 574)
    Public Employment Relations Board (PERB) memos, Mayor's Special Mediation Panel (Archibald Cox Panel).
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - New York City - Tax Package (Box 55, Folder 575)
    Memo to Nelson A. Rockefeller from R. Dunham (Budget).
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - New York State Builders Association, Incorporated, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 576)
    Memos re: legislation to refinance low interest mortgage.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - New York State Teachers Association Legislative Proposals, 1970-1971 (Box 55, Folder 577)
    "Two Teacher Bill," probationary teachers' rights.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Niagara Frontier Transportation Authority, 1967, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 578)
    Memo re: conflicts of interest involving public authorities.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - "Nickerson v. Rockefeller", 1970 (Box 55, Folder 579)
    Nassau County Executive sued to nullify Governor's appointment of member of New York State Civil Service Commission, case dismissed; copy of brief for Governor's appellate division.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - No-Fault Insurance, 1972-1973 (Box 55, Folder 580)
    Correspondence and reports.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Nurses (Box 55, Folder 581)
    Proposed bill submitted by New York State Nurses Association and memos, meeting with Nelson A. Rockefeller, April 28, 1971, Michael Whiteman memo.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Obscenity, 1973-1974 (Box 55, Folder 582)
    Court opinions and memos.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Office for Economic Activity (Federal), 1969 (Box 56, Folder 583)
    Legal services veto correspondence.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Off-Track Betting, 1970-1972 (Box 56, Folder 584)
    Reports, memos, correspondence.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Parks and Recreation, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 585)
    Memos and correspondence re: transfer of park land (Harlem River Park) to City of New York, legislation.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Public Employment Relations Board (PERB), 1969 (Box 56, Folder 586)
    Correspondence concerning Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) news article in which PERB's director of conciliation said Taylor Law not perfect, involvement of legislature in union negotiations, allowing PERB to represent itself in court.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Public Employment Relations Board (PERB), 1967-1973 (Box 56, Folder 587)
    Correspondence, memos, reports.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Per Capita Aid Committee, 1970; Folder 1 of 3 (Box 56, Folder 588)
    State aid to municipalities based on population correspondence.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Per Capita Aid Committee, August 22-October 22, 1969; Folder 2 of 3 (Box 56, Folder 589)
    Correspondence, reports.
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Per Capita Aid Committee, October 29-December 4, 1969; Folder 3 of 3 (Box 56, Folder 590)
  - Issues, 1971-1973 - Pension Reform, 1972-1973 (Box 57, Folder 591)